Christopher Moore collection of Indian Neck Folk Festival and other recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 1: Indian Neck Folk Festival
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #2, April 26, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR048; RXK 4231; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:49:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips and 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; Starting at 00:33:45, the tape has speed issues, running increasingly fast on playback. The reason is unknown but if the machine was a portable unit, the batteries might have drained during the original recording. Speed issues clear up at 0:41:48 when the tape goes from 7 1/2 ips to 3 3/4 ips.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-124.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #3, April 26, 1968, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR049; RXK 4232; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:52:21): analog, 7 1/2 ips; half track stereo, mono audio; 7 in.; Static-like noise permeates the recording for unknown reasons. Some speed instability here and there, especially from 00:50:13 to 00:50:34 where it gets very bad.; See AFC 2016/002: SR053 for a Paul Cadwell performance that was noted as "secretly recorded"; this recording may have been made in a similar way. The latter half or so of the recording (performances by the unidentified musicians) was made in the game room.
      Scope and content: Roy Berkeley; Paul Cadwell (listed on the tape box as P.C.); unidentified group of musicians. Saturday p.m. Original ID number: S-125.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #4, April 26, 1968, May 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR050; RXK 4233; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:27:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips; half track stereo, mono audio; 7 in.; Static-like noise permeates the recording for unknown reasons. At the end of the tape is a brief snippet of Simon and Garfunkel's "At the Zoo." See SR109.
      Scope and content: Pigment (the band name). Also, a jam session recorded in May 1968, after a performance of "Twelfth Night" at Goddard. Steve Rappaport and group. Original ID number: S-126.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR040; RXK 4223; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:38): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Pete Peterson; The Twilighters, Shirley Keller and Lionel Kilberg (bass), Cindy (autoharp); Roy Berkeley. Original ID number: S-116.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR041; RXK 4224; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:51:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips and 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; The speed changes to 3 3/4 ips at 00:44:44:00. The last song is abruptly cut off before finishing.
      Scope and content: Golden Age Retrievers (Tim Woodbridge and the Constitutional Wiretappers (Pete Peterson, Dick Mann, John Burke); Caroline Paton; Bill Hamilton and the Ohio River Boys (Harvey Blau, Geoff Noyes, Dave Kiphuth, Dick Mann, Allen Lee); Bart Hobson. Continued on SR042. Original ID number: S-117.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR042; RXK 4225; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:48:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; A tone at low level can be heard briefly in the right channel at 00:47:39.
      Scope and content: Bart Hobson; Harry and Jeanie West (mandolin and guitar, respectively), Artie Rose (dobro), Winnie Winston (banjo); Al Silverman; Artie Rosenbaum, Allan Block, Ralph Lee Smith; Linda Hughes, Robert Stewart, Karl Eklund. There is a note on the tape box that Paul Cadwell played but refused to be recorded. Continued from SR041; continued on SR043. Original ID number: S-118.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #4, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR043; RXK 4226; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:47:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; At 00:46:34 leftover audio from an incomplete erasure of the tape begins. The audio is very low in level, very short, and included for completeness sake.
      Scope and content: Karl Eklund, Linda Hughes, Robert Stewart; Arnie Feldman, Tom Hayes, Ralph Lee Smith; Guy McKensie; Peter Wernick and the Ad Hoc Mountain Boys (Steve Wernick, banjo; Andy May, mandolin; Steve Arkin, banjo; Tim Woodbridge; Ken Kosek, fiddle); Winnie Winston and Artie Rose. Continued from SR042; continued on SR044. Original ID number: S-119.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #5, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR044; RXK 4227; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Artie Rose and Winnie Winston; Rick and Lorraine Lee, Peter Colby; Peter Colby; Cedar Bog Boys (Ray Prinz, guitar; Tim Woodbridge, guitar; Jack Lund, mandolin; Dave Kiphuth, banjo; Ken Kosek, bass). Continued from SR043. Original ID number: S-120.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #6, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR045; RXK 4228; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Bill Burke; The Star Spangled String Band (Ken Kosek, Andy May); Four Jovial Butchers; Steve Arkin (Andy May, Ken Kosek, and Tim Woodbridge play on "Salt River"). Continued on SR046. Original ID number: S-121.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #7, April 27, 1968, AFC 2016/055: SR046; RXK 4229; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:51:24): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Steve Arkin; Marty Brennan, Ian Buchanan, Steve Winchell; Maxine O'Bramowitz and Lionel Kilberg. Continued from SR045. Original ID number: S-122.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR051; RXK 4234; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:44:06): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Lionel Kilberg; The Golden Nectar Goodtime Band (including the Golden Nectarine and the California Hummingbirds - Jack Lund, Dan Santhouse, Susie Jay, et al); Roy Berkeley, with Bart Hobson on second guitar (joined by Artie Rose on dobro).
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR052; RXK 4235; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:47:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Roy Berkeley; Ed Lipton; The Star Spangled String Band (Andy May, Ken Kosek); Pete Peterson; Shirley Keller.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR053; RXK 4236; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:40:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Shirley Keller; Ohio River Boys (Geoff Noyes, Bill Hamilton, Harvey Blau, Dave Kiphuth, John Conant; joined by Kenny [Ken] Kosek on double fiddle); Peter Colby; Andy Locke.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #4, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR054; RXK 4237; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:14): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Old Reliable String Band (Roy Berkeley, Artie Rose); Bob Stewart and the Eklunds; Rick and Lorraine Lee; Peter Wernick, Bob Stewart. Paul Cadwell's name appears on the tape box, followed by the notation "no tape." Continued on SR055.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #5, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR055; RXK 4238; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:47:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Peter Wernick with Ken Kosek, Artie Rose; Tim Woodbridge and the Constitutional Wiretappers (John Burke, Ralph Lee Smith, Pete Peterson, Tom Hayes); Jack Bertman; Gordon Bok. Continued from SR054.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #6, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR056; RXK 4239; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:45:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Harry and Jeanie West, Artie Rose; Harry and Jeanie West, Dave Kiphuth, Geoff Noyes, Billy Hamilton, Artie Rose; Tom Paley.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #7, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR057; RXK 4240; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:42:23): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Cliff Haslam; Jim McGrath; Jack Parmley.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #1, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR058; RXK 4241; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:43:26): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Bart Hobson; Gordon Bok; Margaret MacArthur.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #2, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR059; RXK 4242; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:32): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.; The audio from 00:45:50-end is a remnant of the original contents of the tape and was recorded at 3 3/4 ips.
      Scope and content: Jim McGrath; Cliff Haslam; Gordon Bok; Andy Leader; Bob Stewart; Karl Eklund. Recorded on Saturday afternoon.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #3, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR060; RXK 4243; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Jim McGrath; Gordon Bok; Cliff Haslam.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #4, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR061; RXK 4244; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:39:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Paul Cadwell (taped during the evening concert).
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TBII #5, circa May 2-4, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR062; RXK 4245; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:46:23): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Jack Bertman; Pete Colby and Andy Leader (Sunday morning). Andy Block [possibly Allan Block]; Pete Peterson; Tim Woodbridge; John Burke; Ralph Lee Smith; Tom Paley (Saturday afternoon).
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TM11 #1, circa May 1-3, 1970, AFC 2016/055: SR063; RXK 4246; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:42:36): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Friday night. Original ID number: S-148.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, TM11 #2, circa May 1-3, 1970, AFC 2016/055: SR064; RXK 4247; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:31:22): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Roy Berkeley; Tim Woodbridge; Rosalie McFall. Saturday, Sunday afternoon. Original ID number: S-149.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, circa May 1-3, 1970, AFC 2016/055: SR065; RXK 4248; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:45:34, Side B: 00:46:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Reed Martin and John Coffey; Shirley Keller and Charlie Wright; Rick and Lorraine Lee; Pete Peterson and Allan Block; Ken Kosek and Andy May; Roy Berkeley; unidentified performer. Note: the reel is labeled S-12; more technical metadata is written on the box. Original ID number: S-150.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, circa May 1-3, 1970, AFC 2016/055: SR066; RXK 4249; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:46:46, Side B: 00:44:30): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: unidentified performers; Fayette Street Ragtime Society (Pete Colby and Mary Rhoades [Mary Faith Rhoads] with Cal Owen; John Coffey, Pete Colby, Tim Woodbridge; Woodbridge, John Coffey, and Rossi [probably Tim Woodbridge, John Coffey, and Neil Rossi]; Gordon Bok; Harry and Jeanie West (Ken Kosek, Dave Kiphuth, Artie Rose). Original ID number: S-151.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, circa May 1-3, 1970, AFC 2016/055: SR067; RXK 4250; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:47:02, Side B: 00:44:10): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Pete Peterson; Dallas Cline and Artie Rose; Dave Jones; Golden Nectar Goodtime Band; Cliff Haslam; Al Schwartz; Margaret MacArthur. Continued on SR068. Original ID number: S-152.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #4, circa May 1-3, 1970, AFC 2016/055: SR068; RXK 4251; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:45:25, Side B: 00:45:45): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Margaret MacArthur; Harry Tuft; Ed Trickett; Bill Burke; Sara Grey, Tim Woodbridge, John Coffey; Barry O'Neil; Ken Kosek, Andy May, Artie Rose, Dave Kiphuth. Continued from SR067; continued on SR069. Original ID number: S-153.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #5, circa May 1-3, 1970, AFC 2016/055: SR069; RXK 4252; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:46:40, Side B: 00:15:27): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Ken Kosek, Andy May, Artie Rose, Dave Kiphuth; Kenneth [probably Ken Kosek] playing solo and with Nick Felder; Nick Felder; Jerry LaSala and Steve [no last name given]. Continued from SR068. Original ID number: S-154.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, MII #1, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR070; RXK 4253; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:44:20): analog, 7 1/2 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.; The last song abruptly cuts off (the tape ran out during the original recording).
      Scope and content: Friday night. Original ID number: S-155.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, MII #2, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR071; RXK 4254; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 01:10:35): analog, 7 1/2 and 3 3/4 ips, full track, mono; 7 in.; The tape speed changes at 00:24:28 from 7 1/2 ips to 3 3/4 ips. The reel consists of 2 5-inch reels spliced together. Tape ends abruptly as it ran out during the original recording.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-156.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, MII #3, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR072; RXK 4255; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Track 1: 00:45:32, Track 2: 00:02:49, Track 3: 00:02:20): analog, 7 1/2 ips and 3 3/4 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.; The tape begins and ends abruptly. One file is a remnant of reel, found after the main recording ended. The speed keeps jumping between 7 1/2 ips and 3 3/4 ips. Recording seems to be an aircheck recorded off FM radio.; File 1 includes collection-related content; files 2 and 3 are commercial music recorded from the radio. Original ID number: S-157.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR073; RXK 4256; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:47:42, Side B: 00:45:31): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The New England Blap Band (Pete Colby, Tim Woodbridge); Roy Berkeley; Maggi Peirce; Allan Block; Shirley Keller; Golden Age Retrievers. Continued on SR074. Original ID number: S-158.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR074; RXK 4257; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:47:50, Side B: 00:47:50): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Golden Age Retrievers; Ted Philips; Karl and Shirley Eklund, and Bob Stewart; Margaret MacArthur; Peter Colby and his All-Stars; Arlington Sacred Harp Singers; Joan Bronfman and [?] Moe Miller; Harry West, Neil Rossi, Artie Rose, Dave Kiphuth, Dick Fegy on guitar. Note: the reel is labeled S-32. Continued from SR073. Original ID number: S-159.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR077; RXK 4260; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:44:13, Side B: 00:46:27): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.; Due to a labeling issue, the digital file designated Side A is for tape Side B, and the digital file designated Side B is for tape Side A. The performers are listed in the correct order for tape sides A and B.
      Scope and content: John Coffey; Sara Grey; Bill Burke; Barbara Carns with Andy May and Rusty Strange (dobro); Betsy Rutherford and John Coffey; John and Tony. Continued on SR075. Original ID number: S-161-B
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #4, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR075; RXK 4258; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:45:49, Side B: 00:45:11): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: John and Tony; Kate Covington; Don Duncan and Jerry Devokaitis; Alice Blistein; David Jones; Nick Apollonio; Andy May; Terry Masterson [announced on the recording but not noted on the tape box]. Continued from SR077; continued on SR076. ID number: S-160.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #5, circa May 7-9, 1971, AFC 2016/055: SR076; RXK 4259; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, Side A: 00:44:53, Side B: 00:26:03): analog, 7 1/2 ips, quarter track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Terry Masterson; Lorraine Lee and Tom Hayes; Cliff Haslam; Bill Nixon and the White House Job; Bob Stewart; The Old Clawgrass Boys; John Coffey. Continued from SR075. Original ID number: S-161-A.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #1, circa May 12-15, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR078; RXK 4261; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 01:29:19): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The Greater New England Blap Band; Maggi Peirce; Dave Kiphuth and Mike Rivers; Betsy Rutherford and John Coffey; Fayette Street Ragtime Band [announced as the Fayette Street Ragtimers] (Pete Colby, Bill Nixon, Cal Owen); Richard Hughes and Walter Scott; Golden Age Retrievers. Continued on SR079. Original ID number: S-162.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #2, circa May 12-15, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR079; RXK 4262; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 01:28:18): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; About 00:08:12, Neil (possibly Neil Rossi) announces "for those of you who are taping" that Paul Cadwell (who was expected to perform next) had asked that he not be recorded. See SR083 for Cadwell's performance, which seems to have been recorded by someone other than Moore.
      Scope and content: Golden Age Retrievers; Jeff Warner; Gail Fratar and Kathy Spencer; Ted Levin; Jay Unger, Bob Roberts, and Jon Wilcox; Sandy Davis and Bill Smith; George and Vaughn Ward; David Jones; The Old Clawgrass Boys. Continued from SR078; continued on SR080. Original ID number: S-163.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #3, circa May 12-15, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR080; RXK 4263; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 01:29:00): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; Track 21 is a very brief remnant of the original audio on the tape and not part of the main (intended) recording.
      Scope and content: Saturday night, closing: The Old Clawgrass Boys; Estelle Ward. Sunday: Margaret MacArthur and Dan MacArthur (her son), joined later by Megan and Gary; Allan Block; Chilly Winds; Roy Berkeley. Continued from SR079. Original ID number: S-164.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #4, circa May 12-15, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR081; RXK 4264; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 01:27:03): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: The New Battleship Potemkin String Ensemble (Reed Martin, banjo; Dick Fegy, guitar; Neil Rossi, fiddle); Shirley Keller and Charlie Wright; Lower Fayette Street Chowder and Marching Sacred Harp Singing Convention and Friends; Jon Wilcox; Rick and Lorraine Lee; Barbara Carns. Continued from SR080; continued on SR082. Original ID number: S-165.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival, #5, circa May 12-15, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR082; RXK 4265; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:40:00): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Barbara Carns; Gordon Bok with Ann (Annie) Muir; Bill Nixon and friends (Pete Colby and Cal Owen). Continued from SR081. Original ID number: S-166.
    - Indian Neck Folk Festival [no reel designation], circa May 12-15, 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR083; RXK 4266; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:18:14): analog, 3 3/4 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Paul Cadwell. See SR078 for the performances before and after Cadwell's performance. Original ID number: S-166-A.
    - Estelle Wade, #1, possibly 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR155; RXK 4338; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:42:00): analog, 3 3/4 ips and 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.; The tape box spines for SR155-SR158 indicate only Estelle Ward, but further details appear on the tape box backs. While the recordings are not identified as part of the Indian Neck Folk Festival or related activities, they include some of the same performers, and sound very much in line with other Festival recordings.
      Scope and content: Estelle Wade and Jerry Epstein, and David Jones, Continued on SR156. Original ID number: S-178.
    - Estelle Wade, #2, possibly 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR156; RXK 4339; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:43:05): analog, 7 1/2 ips and 3 3/4 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: David Jones, Cyril Phillips, Bob White, and Joanie Bronfman and Neal McMillan. Continued from SR155; continued on SR157. See archivist's note for SR155. Original ID number: S-179.
    - Estelle Wade, #3, possibly 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR157; RXK 4340; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:44:37): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Peter Johnson, and Estelle Wade and Jerry Epstein. Continued from SR156; continued on SR158. See archivist's note for SR155. Original ID number: S-180.
    - Estelle Wade, #4, possibly 1972, AFC 2016/055: SR158; RXK 4341; 1 sound tape reel (backcoated polyester, 00:45:00): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Estelle Wade and Jerry Epstein, David Jones, and possibly Cyril Phillips. The recording ends at 00:21:38, and from 00:22:39 to the end there are only test tones. Continued from SR157. See archivist's note for SR155. Original ID number: S-181.
  - Subseries 2: Coffeehouses and other venues
    - Joan Chandos [Joan Baez]; The Boston University Glee Club, 1959, AFC 2016/055: SR084; RXK 4267; 1 sound tape reel (polyester; Side A: 00:48:22, Side B: 00:48:22): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.; This tape is very much a hodge-podge of seemingly unrelated airchecks, recordings of records, and *possibly* a bit of a true live concert sourced from either a radio broadcast or a commercial recording (the first segments of Side A). The body of both sides of the tape is an undated aircheck or airchecks of live Boston Pops broadcast(s). On Side B, the unrelated content continues until about 00:32:07. The segment with Joan Baez starts about 00:34:06, and appears to be a live in-studio performance and interview on an unidentified folk music radio program. She is referred to Joan Chandos in the interview segments. There are no station ID's nor does the host give his name. The recording is very good though her third song is incomplete due to the tape running out. The aircheck continues on SR085.; Side A is content unrelated to the collection. Baez sings and accompanies herself on guitar.
      Scope and content: Songs performed by Joan Chandos (Joan Baez): "Karev Yom" [Israeli; roughly translates as "The Day Draws Near"]. Then the disc jockey plays "Drill Tarriers Drill," a recording by the Weavers, followed by "Fi-Li-Mi-Oo-Re-Ay" (also called "Paddy on the Railway"), also by the Weavers. Interview segments are interspersed between songs. Next songs performed by Baez: "Take This Hammer" and "Black Is the Color" (also called "Black is the Color of My True Love's Hair"). Original ID number: T-8.
    - Joan Chandos [Joan Baez]; Kingston Trio; George Lewis and His Ragtime Band, 1959, AFC 2016/055: SR085; RXK 4268; 1 sound tape reel (acetate; Side A: 00:45:15, Side B: 00:45:15): analog, 7 1/2 ips, half track, mono; 7 in.; This lasts until 00:18:55. After that, the rest of the side is a recording of Side 2 of The Kingston Trio's first LP. Side B consists of the full Kingston Trio LP "from the Hungry i" and two cuts from George Lewis.
      Scope and content: Songs performed by Joan Chandos (Joan Baez): Little Moses; The Troubadour Song; Emmett Till; LaSalle Gardens; Banks of the Ohio; Scarlet Ribbons. Continued from SR084, Side B of the Joan Chandos (Joan Baez) interview and the aircheck from an unknown radio show and station. Original ID number: T-11.
    - Gordon Bok, 1 of 2, November 22, 1969, AFC 2016/055: SR087; RXK 4270; 1 sound tape reel (polyester, 00:51:10): analog, half track, stereo; 7 in.
      Scope and content: Original ID number: S-146.